Here we have the iceCreamTotals object,
这是 iceCreamTotals 对象
which shows the total number of gallons of ice cream
表示优达学城网络团队每位成员
that each member of the Udacity Web team has eaten.
吃掉的冰激凌总量（加仑）
Veronica with 600, Jessica 818, David over 9,000.
Veronica 吃了 600 加仑 Jessica 吃了 818 加仑 David 超过了 9,000 加仑
Richard didn't seem too accurate.
Richard 的似乎不太准确
Let's go ahead add a couple more zeros onto him.
在他的数据后面添加几个零
Wonderful.
很棒
Now let's say I wanted an array of just the keys in this iceCreamTotals object,
现在我想创建一个数组 其中仅包含这个 iceCreamTotals 对象中的键
meaning that I want an array of only Veronica,
即数组中只包含 Veronica
Andrew, Jessica, David, and Richard.
Andrew Jessica David 和 Richard
What we can do is to call Object.keys and pass in the iceCreamTotals object.
我们可以调用 Object.keys 并传入 iceCreamTotals 对象
Let's go ahead and do that.
我们来这么操作
You can see how the return value of calling Object.keys and passing iceCreamTotals,
可以看到传入 iceCreamTotals 后
gives us an array of all the keys in that original object.
为我们提供了由原始对象中的所有键组成的数组
Now, what if we wanted just an array of values of this object?
如果我们只想获得由该对象的值组成的数组呢？
Well similarly, we can just hit
同样 我们可以调用 Object.values
Object.values passing the same object. We can get that array.
并传入相同的对象 就可以获得该数组
And here we have it, we have the array of just the values 600 all the way
我们获得了由值 600 一直到 Richard 的 1000 万
to 10 million for Richard. All right.
组成的数组
So that was just a very clean,
这是非常快速简单的
very quick way of doing things to get the key values.
获得键值方法
What we also could have done was just do a for in loop to build our own array.
我们也可以构建一个 for in 循环来构建数组
Similar to the original setup,
和原来的设置相似
we have the iceCreamTotals object,
我们使用 iceCreamTotals 对象
same information but now this time what we're doing
信息一样 但是这次
is creating our own results array that are going to build up,
我们将自己创建结果数组
and then iterating through the iceCreamTotals object with a for in loop.
然后使用 for in 循环迭代访问 iceCreamTotals 对象
And now, if you check the result array,
如果检查数组
you'll see that it gives us the same output.
就会发现它的输出一样
Let me go ahead and put this side by side.
我并列比较下二者
Notice that the result of the array that we build ourselves gives us
注意 我们自己构建的数组输出
the same output as the Object.keys call we made originally.
和之前构建的 Object.keys 调用的输出一样
Using Object.keys gives us the same result as if we loop through it ourselves,
使用 Object.keys 的结果和自己循环访问的结果一样
but it's a little bit more readable and also a lot less code to write.
但是更容易读懂 并且代码更少